{
    "ab1234": {
     "subject": "Test your Spanish antonym skills",
      "help": "Choose the word that is the opposite of the displayed word",
     "data": [
      {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "frío",
        "answers": ["caliente", "burrito", "escuela", "perro"],
        "correctAnswer": "caliente"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "arriba",
        "answers": ["abajo", "lápiz", "verde", "nosotros"],
        "correctAnswer": "abajo"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "cerca",
        "answers": ["lejos", "gato", "caminar", "helado"],
        "correctAnswer": "lejos"
      },
       {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "alto",
        "answers": ["bajo", "chico", "brincar", "malo"],
        "correctAnswer": "bajo"
      },
       {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "izquierda",
        "answers": ["derecha", "azúl", "inteligente", "casa"],
        "correctAnswer": "derecha"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "ganar",
        "answers": ["perder", "visitar", "ella", "borrador"],
        "correctAnswer": "perder"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "verdadero",
        "answers": ["falso", "lápiz", "morado", "comer"],
        "correctAnswer": "falso"
      },
      {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "rico",
        "answers": ["pobre", "compartir", "reloj", "helado"],
        "correctAnswer": "pobre"
      },
       {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "mojado",
        "answers": ["seco", "mujer", "comida", "bien"],
        "correctAnswer": "seco"
      },
       {
        "questionType": "opposite",
        "question": "largo",
        "answers": ["corto", "amarillo", "caliente", "contento"],
        "correctAnswer": "corto"
      }
    ]
    }
  
}